Dexter Crago Software Developer

My Personal Website

406) 241-7556

Profile

I'm Dexter, a full-stack web developer with a strong grasp of programming fundamentals, lots of experience fixing my own code, and a strong drive to continue learning and improving my skills. Feel free to check out my personal website ♂ to learn more about me and how I can start adding value to your team right away!

Education

Software Development, The Odin Project

Aug 2023 - May 2024

Project-based learning

Bachelor of Science, *Montana State University*

Aug 2021 - May 2023

High School Science Education

Bachelor of Science, *University of Montana*

Aug 2018 - May 2021

High School Science Education

High School Diploma, Big Sky High School

Aug 2014 - Jun 2018

International Baccalaureate Diploma

Organizations

Montana Indian Ministries, Summer Camp Leader

Jun 2015 – present

Co-lead 50+ camp counselors

Morning Star Elementary School, Tech Club Leader

Feb 2022 – May 2022

Led a weekly after-school tech club for elementary students





Professional Experience

Stevensville High School, Student Teacher

Jan 2023 – Apr 2023

Responsible for over 100 students

Montana Club, Server

Jun 2015 - Mar 2021

Served at least 100 clients per day

City Life Community Center, Youth Worker

Jun 2018 - Jun 2020

Coordinated trips for 20+ students